{"instructions": ["When you are ready, click <strong>Continue</strong>."], "feedback": true, "holdfeedback": false, "feedbackdur": 600, "serveraudio": false, "estimatedduration": 4, "randomize": false, "isi": 600, "volume": [{"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "You did not pass the screening. Let us give it another try?", "choices": ["Yes, let's do it."]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "The headphones are usually marked as left/right to indicate which ear they are for. Did you make sure the right headphone is in your right ear, and the left headphone is in your left ear? It is very important for making the correct decisions.", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue."]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "Are you in a quiet room?", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue"]}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Now adjust your computer volume up to a comfortable (but not too loud) level.", "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/volume.wav", "choices": ["I have adjusted the volume, let's continue"]}], "trials": [{"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_2_M1XJlo2bEk8SFDdQ.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_1_eGfYYSjOG8OXCAZf.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_1_kyZXdyGzOMsAa9kg.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_1_mEv75dTqAH6z8sRP.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_2_RPlh9kcI2PlwC8j1.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_2_xlADhKoxKpsMqZ8T.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_1_Kg42YqKbAtklAfLD.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_2_RNcetGOzYS8GugLW.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_1_fqjrBGC2G6N7oPrP.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_2_epnP0vWPaLx4aCAC.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_2_tWDckSDjvLlTp4qV.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_1_rfJQHANOQN6mRohL.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_1_CPVvPz0ZpMKH1qth.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_2_ODNHOHSG9nggdzBw.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/demo_2/128us_2_MV58liRfGG1EyPTG.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}]}